spacepaintings.com 1999-04-27

# Channel21 Online Privacy Policy

The policies below are applicable to the above-named online services (collectively the "Service") produced and maintained by Channel21 Productions, Inc. ("Channel21"). 

Channel21 collects personally identifying information only during (i) web page signup and (ii) subscription registration. In addition, information is collected in certain portions of the Service in which guests specifically and knowingly provide such information along with content submissions, community postings (i.e., chat or bulletin boards), suggestions, or voting. Channel21 may use such information for its internal purposes, including but not limited to editorial and feedback purposes. In the event Channel21 plans to publicly post any such information on a site, guests are provided prior notification of such posting. 

Information submitted at the time of registration or submission may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by Channel21 and may be shared with companies that have been pre-screened by Channel21. If a guest objects to such use for any reason, he/she may stop that use -- either by e-mail request or by modifying his/her registration information online. 

**Cookies** are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes while at the site. Cookies make Web-surfing easier by, among other things, saving your passwords, purchases, and preferences for you. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and you'll find cookies at most major Web sites. 

Cookies help make Channel21 better, by showing how and when guests use the site. Many content improvements and updates are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. 

Here are some other examples of how Channel21 uses cookies:   

  * A cookie lets the Service remember that you've registered, which allows us to speed up your future activities at our sites. 
  * Similarly, if there are any stores within the Service, a temporary cookie tracks which products you've selected while shopping. The cookie expires once you're done shopping. Letting it do the record-keeping saves you the trouble of entering information over and over again during a single visit. If you decline this cookie, you may have difficulty ordering your selections. 

The cookie itself does not contain any personally identifying information although it may enable Channel21 to relate a user's use of the Service to personally identifying information that has previously been submitted by the user, if any. 

You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. These cookies are sent from third-party computers and are subject to such third parties' policies. 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, it is likely that most areas of the site will not function properly if you do so. 

Channel21 reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying guests, through a notice posted on the Service or by email, of the existence of a new privacy policy or any updates.
